{

    "level1": 
    [
        {
            "problem": "Slovensko",
            "solution": "Bratislava"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Poľsko",
            "solution": "Waršava"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Rusko",
            "solution": "Moskva"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Nemecko",
            "solution": "Berlin"
        },
        {
            "problem": "USA",
            "solution": "Washington"
        },


        {
            "problem": "2*4",
            "solution": "8"
        },
        {
            "problem": "5*8",
            "solution": "40"
        },
        {
            "problem": "sqrt(100)",
            "solution": "10"
        },
        {
            "problem": "2*8-15",
            "solution": "1"
        },
        {
            "problem": "20^2",
            "solution": "400"
        },

        {
            "problem": "Štvorec",
            "solution": "4"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Trojuholník",
            "solution": "3"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Šesťuholník",
            "solution": "6"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Hviezda",
            "solution": "5"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Kruh",
            "solution": "0"
        },

        {
            "problem": "Azia",
            "solution": "Čína"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Európa",
            "solution": "Španielsko"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Južná Amerika",
            "solution": "Kolumbia"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Afrika",
            "solution": "Somálsko"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Severná Amerika",
            "solution": "Kanada"
        },

        {
            "problem": "India",
            "solution": "Taj Mahal"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Peru",
            "solution": "Machu Picchu"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Taliansko",
            "solution": "Colosseum"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Anglicko",
            "solution": "Tower Clock"
        },
        {
            "problem": "Francúzsko",
            "solution": "Eifelová veža"
        }
    ]
}